Guide to the Larry Rivers Papers 1952-2010 MSS 293
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series V: Source Material
  - Subseries A: Source File
    - Source File 23, undated (Box 105, Folder 7)
      Statue of Liberty, Vanity Fair
    - Source File 34, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      "Homage to Picasso".
    - Source File 37, undated (Box 105, Folder 9)
      Various Photos of Transvestites.
    - Source File 38, undated (Box 105, Folder 10)
      Rolling Stones & "Gimme Shelter".
    - Source File 39, undated (Box 105, Folder 11)
      Norman Mailer.
    - Source File 41, undated (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Source File 63, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      The Mulgraves.
    - Source File 83, undated (Box 105, Folder 14)
      Music.
    - Source File 86, undated (Box 105, Folder 15)
      Dutch Masters.
    - Oversize Source Drawer 3, undated (Box 105, Folder 16)
      "Me II".
  - Subseries B: By Subject
    - "75 Years Later: Art at the Armory", 1988 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Abdul-Jabbar, Kareem, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Africa, undated (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Art & the Artist (Peruvian Street Art), undated (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Berdie, undated (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Berdie, undated (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - City Junket, undated (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Deshuk, Daria, undated (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Dillon, Lorraine, undated (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Duck Farm, undated (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Ertegun, Ahmet, undated (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - History of Matzah: The Story of the Jews, undated (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Japanese with Ice Cream Cone, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Jazz, undated (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - JC Penney, undated (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Kaiser, Mrs. Allie, undated (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy Family, undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Kinka Warriors, undated (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Last Civil War Veteran, undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Last Civil War Veteran, undated (Map-case 4.E, Folder 5)
    - Lee, Casy, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Magician of Lublin, undated (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Magician of Lublin, undated (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Make Believe Ballroom, undated (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Memory, undated (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Memory, undated (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Source Photos, undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Modernist Times, undated (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Newman, Barnett, undated (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Nikolich, Peter, 1960 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Old Sicilian Story, undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Public and Private, 1958, undated (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Revolutionary Soldiers, undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Rivers at Work, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Roots, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Shelly, undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - A Slave Auction, undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Stones, undated (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Tarot Project, undated (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Tattoos, undated (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Theatre Seats, undated (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Source Files, undated (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Source Files, undated (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Webster, undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - What's For Sale, undated (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Woman and Women, Spanking, undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
- OVERSIZE Series VI: Clippings
  - General Clippings, 1968, undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Map-case 4.E, Folder 6)
  - "A Painter Among Poets", 1991 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    by Lana Jokel, in View (March 1991).
- OVERSIZE Series VII: Music Materials
  - Foss, Lukas, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Performance Press, Flyers, Posters and Invitations, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Performance Press, Flyers, Posters and Invitations, undated (Map-case 4.E, Folder 7)
  - Sheet Music: "The Moon, the Coon, and the Little Octoroon", undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
- OVERSIZE Series VIII: Administrative Files
  - Appointment Calendar Pages, 1989-1990 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Award of Distinction, The Five Towns Music and Art Foundation, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Awards and Honors, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    Honorary Doctorate of Fine Arts from the Corcoran School of Art.
  - Awards and Honors, 1991-92, undated (Box 108, Folder 9)
    Kentucky Colonel's Commission, from the Commonwealth of Kentucky; Honorary Doctorate of Arts from Long Island University; Certificate of Appreciation from the American Cancer Society; Certificate of Merit from the Society of Illustrators.
  - Awards and Honors, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    Distinguished Achievement Award, from Writers and Artists for Peace in the Middle East.
  - Commemorative Plaque, from the National Women's Division of the American Jewish Congress, 1966 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Other Artists), 1967, '95, undated (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Other Artists), 1968, undated (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Rivers), 1970-93, undated (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Rivers), 1981-92, undated (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Rivers), 1968-1980 (Map-case 4.E, Folder 8)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Rivers), 1981-1988 (Map-case 4.E, Folder 9)
  - Flyers, Posters, Announcements, Promotional Materials (Rivers), 1990-97, undated (Map-case 4.E, Folder 10)
- OVERSIZE Series IX: Financial Records
  - Financial Ledgers, 1976-1977 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1977-1979 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1993-1995 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Tax Papers, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 16)
- OVERSIZE Series XII: Real Estate
  - Casa Luna / Lomo, Mexico, 1979-1982; 1 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Southampton House Leases, 1986, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 18)
- OVERSIZE Series XIII: Personal Files
  - Photographs, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    Photographs by:
    Jill Krementz